

Student at Ranken Technical College

ScottHardy4555@outlook.com

+1(314)-825-7168

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/scott-hardy-0b805b246 Github: https://github.com/ScottHardy4555

Portfolio: https://scotthardy4555.github.io/

Self-taught programmer with seven years of total work experience and four years of programming. Proficient in programming languages such as C#, JavaScript, HTML5, and CSS as wells as introductory experience with Java and C++. Excellent interpersonal skills and experience tutoring individuals in computer science. Hard worker with an emphasis on teamwork and attention to detail.

Key Skills

- C#
- JavaScript
- Java
- HTML5
- Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
- React.js
- Interpersonal Communication
- Problem Solving
- Self-Development
- Mathematical Aptitude

Professional Experience

August 2022 -

The UPS Store, Chesterfield, Missouri, United States

- Provide mailing and shipping services to customers.
- Communicate shipping procedures and requirements.
- ${}^{\bullet}$ Responsible for solo operation of the store from open to
- Provide solutions to unique customer inquiries and requests.

February 2019 -April 2022 Production Associate

Panera Bread

Store Cashier

- Cooperated with coworkers to uphold excellent standards of customer service.
- Served as trainer for new coworkers.
- Provided leadership as on-shift quality control coordinator.

May 2021 -November 2021

Line Cook

The Wolf Cafe

- Established effective communication with coworkers to consistently maintain a high standard of quality.
- Work long hours at a high intensity pace.
- Maintained a careful attention to detail.
- Responsible for advanced preparation of ingredients while keeping the workplace immaculate.

Education

Computer Programming

Ranken Technical College| August 2022 - May

2024

High School Diploma

Parkway West | August 2014 - May

2018

Accomplishments

Achived second place at the 2018 Vex Robotics State Competition serving as the team's senior programmer.